Two lives. Changed forever. With just one click.
Twinsters is a family, documentary film directed by Samantha Futerman.
Adopted from South Korea, raised on different continents & connected through social media,
Samantha & Anaïs believe that they are twin sisters separated at birth.
Self, played by Anais Bordier.
Self, played by Samantha Futerman.
Self, played by Kanoa Goo.
Twinsters is a 2015 documentary film which covers the true-life story of identical twin sisters, separated at birth, discovering each
other on-line, meeting, confirming their identity with a DNA test, and exploring aspects of their background together.
The film was released as a biography genre documentary on
March 15, 2015, at South by Southwest.
After that, the film was made available through various streaming
platforms, including Netflix, iTunes and Freeform.
In September 2016, the network ABC bought a comedy based on the Twinsters
documentary from the creators responsible for Funny or Die.
The film explores themes of twin sister, adoption, woman
director, sisterhood, international adoption.